Hey oh boy this is gonna be so much fun
I can whip the Bobby get here for four
days I mean I picked the most beautiful
spot in the park for us that's your
hangout maybe have some nice butt sex oh
yes mmm oh no oh he can Bobby now k
Sonic play it cool play it cool don't
make it look like he won't but sex out
in the first minute hahaha hello bid oh
hello Bobby oh but you make you bang
your cute little ass oh oh yeah mmm oh
absolutely I was thinking I you know I I
called you out here for your day oh oh
boy do I bid well have we play hide and
seek lie well it's just that you and me
never get to hang out much so I mean we
you know with you being rich for the
last four months you you know been
buying places in China and in Russia
Germany just want to hang out have
enough fun you know okay okay Bobby I'm
gonna count 15 I you know you County 10
I'll go hot okay okay okay Bobby look
away okay one two three four oh I
think you're trying to please your heart
seven six five nine ten Oh over here oh
we get good this would be the good
right here
okay beat I'm coming ahahah ahahah will
you add I found you oh but I thought you
were here where are you Oh Oh is she
where are you I can see where are you I
can find you he wow I can see me from
behind the I should dock so
that why I can't see me ah you can hide
from me but you can't hide that cute
little ass oh oh I don't run oh oh this
is a good spot you had ditch where are
you ahaha where did you go now are you
behind here oh oh are you here where are
you Oh Oh Barbie so you did why are you
oh I found you oh outta here
found you oh oh I got you
bend ova bowl ah